Finding Aid for the Newton Ford Raines Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Newton Ford Raines Collection
1875-1876
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0354
.02 linear feet
Biographical Sketch
Newton Ford Raines was a member of the first class at Vanderbilt University in October, 1875. Ada Raines, his daughter, donated the materials in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains materials related to Newton Ford Raines admission to Vanderbilt University.
- Folder 1
  - Order For Matriculation for N. F. Raines
    - October 5, 1875
- Folder 2
  - Report Cards of N. F. Raines
    - December 23, 1875
    - January 31, 1876
    - April 29, 1876
    - June 21, 1876
    - July 29, 1876 [including transcript of evaluation]